

Gian Sonia Backend Developer

- **Q** 082321634181
- giansonia555@gmail.com
- ▶ linkedin.com/in/gian-sonia-744059222/
- ♥ Kota Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

SUMMARY

With three years of dedicated experience as a Backend Developer, I have a successful track record of completing major projects, including the creation of motor showroom websites for leading clients. I am ready to bring this expertise and experience to create innovative and captivating solutions for your company

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer Full Stack Developer

09/2023 - 02/2024

SIPSIS (Sistem Informasi Presensi SMP Persis)

- Creating a website for the academic needs of SMP Persis Gandok.
- Develop a attendance system capable of sending attendance notifications to parents' WhatsApp utilizing the Twilio API.

Freelancer Fullstack Developer

04/2023 - 06/2023

SISMAC (Sistem Informasi Mandiri Utama Finance Community)

- Developing websites for each showroom in collaboration with Mandiri Utama Finance.
- Analyzing the challenges and opportunities present in one of the showrooms.
- Creating a tailored system that aligns with the specific requirements of that showroom.
- · Building the system with the assistance of the Laravel framework and MySQL

EDUCATION

Madrasah Aliyah Negeri 2 Kota Tasikmalaya	2016 - 2019
Teknik Informatika STMIK Tasikmalaya	2019 - 2021
Teknik Informatika Universitas Perjuangan Tasikmalaya	2022 - 2024

SKILLS

CSS	Intermediate	MySql	Intermediate
HTML	Advanced	Javascript	Intermediate
Codelgniter	Intermediate	PHP	Advanced
Laravel	Advanced		